I sell premium catering experiences to private clients.
We do about 2.8 million this year with 40% net profit
and I would like to be 8 million in two years.
Let's go.
Making change seasonally.
So we do about 65% of our annual revenue in six months.
And if I don't solve this,
I either say no to demand in summer
or I am overstaffed in winter.
I'll say is that this is a feature,
not a bug of the industry that you're in, right?
Same thing as lawn care guys,
same thing as guys who do snow plowing.
It's just a, it's a super common thing.
I've considered popping up corporate catering setting.
I don't want to get distracted.
Like what's one of your content?
I don't want to chase the woman in the red dress.
What we need to replace is the difference
between volatility and risk.
So you can have something that is volatile, but not risky.
So if we know it's going to happen, then we can predict it.
If we can predict it, we can plan for it, right?
What I would like to do is just focus all of your time
on how do we double PPC and probably get meta ads going.
Like if you did nothing else this year,
doubled PPC and just cracked meta ads, you'd hit your goal.
If you can double the business doing one thing, why do four?
I mean, the whole point of theory of constraints is focus.
And it's just being able to say all the things
you say no to.
Like if you can just say like,
I'm not looking at this anymore
because this is just a feature of my business.
And I'm so grateful because all my competitors
will be distracted by the shiny object.
Let them worry about that while you just keep crushing it.